In the mighty name of Jesus Christ !
National Healing Campaign in Singapore with Prophet T.B. Josua
In Jesus Christ's name !
Come here !
You need deliverance, she needs deliverances !
You have spirit of lizard.
I can smell it.
In Jesus' name.
National Healing Campaign in Singapore with Prophet T.B. Josua
Wow, can you see !
Who are you ? I am the King of Asia.
No, no
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ !
You are free !
Thank you Jesus !
My name is Margaret Tansinwah. I am 39 years old. I am from Singapore. I am a Singaporean.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, he prophesied that I had an evil spirit of lizard.
Which was very true, because...
Both me and my daughter had the evil spirits, because I wanted to kill my daughter.
The spirit of lizard in me has gone out, and I am set free, my daughter has also been set free.
As you have been set free, and delivered, what is your promise to God.
My promise is to serve the Lord.
Music : I am telling what I know about the Jesus of Nazareth.
My name is Margaret Tansinwah. I am 39 years old. I am a Singaporean.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me
He prophesied that there's a spirit of lizard in me, and in my daughter.
It is very true.
The evil spirit in me would ask me to harm my daughter, I would get angry, and I would want to kill her.
After the man of God, Prophet T.B.Joshua prayed for me,
I no longer need to take all this medicine, to ? I am set free.
Hallelujah ! Put your hands together for Jesus Christ !
All of these are very expensive drugs.
These are very wanted (highly sought after) by drug addicts.
Thay are all sleeping pills, and they are not sold over the counter.
Do you mean that you use to take these before your deliverance ?
Yes, you can a lot of medicines ....
Medicine from...
Nasal drips.
Bronchitis
Sleeping pills
My daughter has to put nasal drop, when she was 3
Can you tell us what happens to you yesterday ?
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed over you.
I was set free.
We no longer need this medicine.
I slept like a baby.
Hallelujeh ! Put your hands together for our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ !
We are set free and I love my daughter.
Madam, how do you feel today ?
I feel great, I woke up without any headaches.
Amen, put your hands together for Jesus.
Praise the Lord !
I confirm that the evil spirit in me is gone,
because I don't hear any voices.
You mean you are free in Jesus name.
Yes I am free, in Jesus name.
Hallelujeh ! Let's clap for Jesus Christ !
Thank you very much !
God bless you in Jesus name.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today.
And stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies,
deliverances, service and testimonies from the SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV, changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.